And I'll call the reggae to meet my city council from Monday, September 16th, 2020, before.
Public input, I'm just going to personal parenthesis.
And then three guns list.
Let's ship group.
Second.
I'm 27, 25-year-old, one of the justings that's made carry over to actually carry over and we're going to come break phones and prove that this will be your 23.4 and not use until you use by 630.4, spend it in just a year 24.5.
No, it's too true.
Second.
Thank you.
I want to wrestle with you.
Hi.
John.
Parker.
Hi.
Sort of contract for DJ services, with all of you entertainment during the third annual team life player in amount of $200 of the ender.
Good evening.
Thank you.
I would like to start by introducing myself.
My name is Alexander Space.
I'm a used librarian at the Miami Public Library.
I started in March.
One of the first things I'd like to record.
I said about programming.
Was that she said she wanted to continue doing the team life fair.
It's always the first Saturday and October.
I've done my best to learn about the past human affairs.
To kind of figure out what work to want.
We could work on to do better.
One of the things suggested was that we have a DJ or a band.
That'd be a great way to attract more attendees.
Create a more fun atmosphere.
So we narrowed it down to offer you entertainment.
Somehow I thought you had my friend of you.
Often entertainment is a local entertainer.
It has been to multiple local venues and events.
Bringing their own equipment for indoor and outdoor use.
They're giving us a deep discount.
Taking a consideration or a limited budget in the events.
Cause which is team mental health and community connections.
They will perform a total of four hours.
Which is the entirety of the event for a cost of $200.
That $200 will come directly from the youth department team programming budget.
Which I've been saving since July for this event.
Have any questions?
Thank you.
Nine.
For questions or proposals or a P.
For fixed-based operators services FBO.
Specialized aviation service operations.
At the moment.
Regional Air Force.
This is just an update of where we're at on your procedure.
We'll be with Alfred FBO to present.
and a lot of people involved in this packet.
What this will do is it allows somebody to come in
and essentially run a business inside the airport.
So this packet was presented to the airport
for the worry on the night.
They had heard it was some changes.
The packet is out now.
They'll choose to operate.
And then we're hoping to get that back
before the airport.
You have to just have to use it on the 15th.
And then bring it back to your airport log.
So the airport board on the 15th?
Yes.
And back to us home to the 21st.
That's the airport.
I know that people reach out to them
and different things.
So I just asked them to have to do it.
If anyone were asked so.
And this way this was put together.
It should be able to make the city and the successful.
Do options they can do at all in kind of the same way
and they fully run it?
Or they can part of that, kind of, all of the car
and just provide a one service for two services.
So if they part of not just do one or two services
to handle the rest, what kind of do we
talking about the city would have to be responsible for?
So you said that they were going to take a couple of things
out there and the city would handle the rest.
What is the city handling?
Well, it really depends on what they put their proposal.
Because they might not know we offer flexible.
Or they may want to run the fuel service.
If they don't want to do the fuel service,
we'll continue to try to keep maintaining the fuel itself.
We don't want loose control of the fuel.
We can't do the fuel rather than the best.
Okay, do we always just work on one group or is there multiple groups that have lifted this?
We don't want that.
Nobody's replied yet.
Yeah, we don't know.
We don't want that.
So there's not a day right now.
Right.
OK.
Understood.
We take it.
Yep.
Thank you.
10 resolutions.
So you see your 2024 dash.
0.8.
The verification of the certification, the codification.
Okay, another.
My hope one would go, that warns us to include supplement 18.
So we're required by law to, I see here,
a radar book that has all the warmances.
The Unicode does that for us.
And if prepared, the light is supplemented.
This is just proving that, then once it's approved,
we're going to officially make the changes in all of our books.
Which, and then the law requires us to keep a updated coffee
at the accounting law library.
We'll update the one of this, this resolution.
Okay, so they just don't talk about it?
Do we do this last year?
We do it twice a year.
Yeah.
It's a close trip route.
Oh, it's a bit expensive.
It's a bit expensive.
I apologize.
I thought she asked if she needed to make a motion.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do this.
Sorry.
Okay, Jim.
Hi.
Park.
Well, I have a resolution.
CC.
2024.
That year of nine is fourth.
The grant proposal to environmental protection agency
for restoring George Francis to review park nature.
So this is a resolution that was stems from the conversation
that we had a couple of meetings.
The project.
The resolution would allow us to have control kind of as we asked.
If there's any other changes like to make it, and now it would be the time.
I thought it would be as if we'd prove the resolution.
And then we could go after two grants for the city themselves.
And that would be fiber and for solar panels
that would be a good rich in glindance here in glindance.
You got information from me to, you know,
if that's the route we want to go.
So.
The deadline is not to celebrate energy,
but the larger the track one is a large project.
So we could do fiber and we could do solar at the least.
A smaller one is only those are not what I would consider
or we would we want to waste our time on.
I would do this.
The fiber and the solar would be over 10 mil.
Thinking what I was looking at today
after time on top.
I'm thinking the solar would be around like 10.5.
The fiber would be close to probably 17 mil.
The prep days.
You're going to be here part.
Going to the solar and fiber.
I want any questions on that now.
Anybody else?
Any questions?
Should we went on that?
Motion to approve.
Hi.
All right.
12.
I don't do business of anybody.
As a result, since the posting of this agenda.
13 staff reports.
14 mayor council community announcements.
I mean.
No.
I'm going to the sit and shop.
Coming up on Thursday.
Downtown Main Street.
Go to the local shop.
Go sit and shop.
Cali, do you want to talk about the event last night?
Saturday night.
I'm going to make it right for a while from Hayley to get to a while to hear some comments about it.
So it's a tell you about the seven shop that we've got the bull bash coming October 12.
So we ride down town.
This is going to be a big undertaking for all of our people from every department.
But it could be really cool if we live.
We live, we'll be taking some selfie going Saturday.
There was a little problem there, but we're going to take care of it.
We'll be ready tomorrow.
I think that they can be a part of it.
So you have plenty of those people to come back.
Hey, what about the downtown October thing?
You're going to announce that.
Tell me, you just said.
The bull.
No, no, no, no, the dinner.
The dinner, I'll make sure.
Well, that'll be October 18th.
Is that correct?
Yep.
October 18th.
In the same street.
They have to 250.
It seats this time.
That was 125 last time.
So 150 in those tickets will come on Sunday.
Thank you so much.
15.
So many of those communications.
I'm happy to announce.
And this is kind of in our grants there, which, um,
Kyle and I are going to wear our grants there are two shirts.
Someday we'll get a big grant.
We'll maybe get blessed.
Thank you.
England.
Um, we'll have to get some t-shirts made.
But I'm happy to announce that my public library is one of 62 organizations nationwide.
To receive the national endowment for the arts.
Big grant to host the discussion centered around the grapes of wrath.
And this theme where we live.
This program aims to engage the community in reading and discussions.
Preserving local histories and fostering cultural dialogue.
Various activities including book discussions, workshops and films screening and
public middle project will take place from September 2024 to June 2025.
Coffee's at the book will be given out at the end of the counseling tonight.
We have limited large print coffees and some audio recordings of the live play.
If you guys would like that.
The NEAB read initiative supported by Arts Midwest and the National Endowment of Arts
Promote shared reading experiences to inspire conversations and artistic expressions.
in the United States.
So I'm excited.
They haven't talked about this at ITC, so you know.
I'm excited.
Pick up your good one, your way out.
There you go.
Please don't share a big grant that we know about.
It's not officially yet.
I'm just going to say, you said we're in our grant area.
And that's the fact.
We, we, we've, last week, gone around with the,
uh, home health conference in Tulsa.
We talk a lot of people there.
We got a lot of stuff.
We're home in the offer.
And there's a lot of money out there.
And, uh, I was being in the sweet spot here with our travel partners.
It really happened.
And, uh, so, I know.
We're going this health.
We're going after a bunch of those.
And, I think we have a pretty good opportunity on a lot of those.
So, and these aren't, these aren't,
you're 125,000, big thousand.
These are millions.
And, uh, we're sitting really good shape.
I started to love them.
So, frustrating is hopefully continues to be there.
Because it could be some big announcements going.
16 adjournment.
Motion to adjourn.
Second.